{
    "subject": "resource/Inge_Morath",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1923-05-27",
    "human_readable": "Inge Morath was born on May 27, 1923.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8244877457618713,
            "question": "When was Inge Morath born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8030858039855957,
            "question": "What century was Inge Morath born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7400572299957275,
            "question": "How old was Inge Morath on May 27, 1983?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7263185381889343,
            "question": "If Inge Morath was born on May 27th, what day of the week would it be in a year that has 366 days?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5070216059684753,
            "question": "What month and day was Inge Morath born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4492005407810211,
            "question": "Is Inge Morath's birthdate in the spring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41279926896095276,
            "question": "In what year did Inge Morath come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3774229884147644,
            "question": "Is Inge Morath's birthday before or after June 1st?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.328254759311676,
            "question": "What is Inge Morath's birth date expressed as MM/DD/YYYY?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3217984437942505,
            "question": "If today is October 26, 2023, how many years older is Inge Morath than someone born on that date?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Inge Morath was born on May 27, 1923.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4938_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Inge Morath's birth date expressed as MM/DD/YYYY?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4938_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Inge Morath's birthday before or after June 1st?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4938_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Inge Morath come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4938_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4938_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents which state that Inge Morath was born on May 27, 1923."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}